ajebomarket.com 2015-05-10

# Privacy Policy

* * *

All information provided by you is only used to ensure the best possible shopping experience. All information is strictly confidential. Your personal information will not be shared, circulated, nor modified in any way without your previous consent.

If you place an order with us, we request certain personal information. You must provide contact information (such as name, email and delivery address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date and the 3 digit security code). We use this information for billing purposes and to complete your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use your contact information. Your telephone number is required for shipping purposes in case our courier needs to contact you regarding the delivery.

We use third-party web beacons (Google Analytics) from Google to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make significant changes to this policy, we will notify you here and by a notice on the website in general.

Cookies are pieces of information which a website transfers to your computers hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make a web site more useful by personalizing information for visitors and by storing information about your preferences on our site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major websites use them to provide useful features for their customers. It is our policy to use cookies only for the following purposes:

  * To identify you
  * To customize our site for you
  * To help improve navigation

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to reject cookies. However, you will not be able to take full advantage of our web site if you do so.

We use tracking technology to better understand site traffic patterns and use. However, none of the information collected via tracking technology is personally identifiable information 

**Disclaimer**

Ajebo Online Megastore strives, to the fullest extent possible, to provide accurate and updated content on this website. Unfortunately, there may occasionally be price changes, sold out goods and other unintentional errors on our site. We reserve the right not to be liable for these errors or changes and neither Ajebo Online Megastore nor any employee or representative of Ajebo Online Megastore will be liable for damages arising from the use of this website or the products sold here.

Any dispute arising between a customer and Ajebo Online Megastore will be settled in accordance with Nigerian Legislation.
